Nwalozie Princess

A strong and self reliant young lady who is restless and determined with a lot of poise, charisma, decipherable and meaningfully creating an amazing environment with co-workers, very empathetic with a humane spirit alongside effective spirit of teamplay, resourceful, social media savvy, very strong communication skills, learnable as well as teachable with over four years working experience to show for it.



- 🔽 nwalozieprincess@gmail.com 🌙 08133444288
- 🗥 No 7b Akeem adetoro, lifecamp, FCT, Abuja Abuja

Education

Sep 2015 - Oct 2019

Second class upper In history and international relations. Bachelor of Arts in Education.

University of Nigeria, Nsukka., Enugu state

Employment

Jan 2018 - Oct 2018

Secretary

Esomchukwu law chambers, Wetheral road, Owerri IMO State

I oversaw all computer and Microsoft documents relating to court cases in addition to effective discharge of assigned duties with little or no errors.

Exhibited spirit of teamplay with co-workers and created an amazing relationship with my employer.

Dec 2019 - Oct 2021

On Air personality

Darling Fm Radio, Owerri, Imo state, Owerri

Creation of premium on air content as well as airing them to listeners satisfaction.

Newscasting and sustenance of listeners interest through strong fluent flow of communication as well as virtual working relationship.

Creative use of social media thought tweets and retweets, hashtags, catchy captions and engagements.

Generation of revenue and sales through production of radio jingles and paid adverts as well as product marketing.

Nov 2021 - Aug 2022

Admin personnel

West Africa examination council, Ilorin, kwara state.

Effective discharge of duties.

Participation in the examination and coordination of WASSCE 2022 for school candidate.

Showed a hardworking spirit to co-workers admiration which earned me several compliments and promotion.

Feb 2022 - Oct 2022

Social media manager

Cozyflopsnigeria, Ibadan

Engaged social media handles with content to draw customers attention through premium writeup.

shooting amazing video snippets of products and advertising on social media to

maximize sales. Created emails as well as answering mails swiftly. Creation of mindblowing newsletters for the social media community. Strong communication skills Analytical and problem solving skills **Skills** Strong leadership and team play spirit English language and Igbo Languages languages Effective interactions with **Hobbies** Reading and writing is my big flair interesting people Surfing the internet **Certificates** Most outstanding student of the year in the faculty of social sciences, Sep 2019 University of Nigeria. Certificate of completion of course in fire and safety from Florence Academy, UK Nov 2018 Outstanding kinswoman, Ikeduru students association, University of Nigeria. Writer of the month at writer's hub. **Achievements** Host and owner of the "Drunk n Tipsy Podcast" available on Spotify and Anchor **Extracurricular activities** A very devoted writer with the perfect niche to catch readers attention. Loves to work out at the gym and improve on all round wellbeing. scholarly work on effect of female genital mutilation as it affects young girls across Africa(2018-2019) (Nwalozie P.c).

> Punctual, very straightforward and truthful, Amazing accommodating

References available upon request.

personality.

Qualities

References